你可能认为  生命周期非常的重要
You may be thinking, lifecycles are really important.
但是这一节  我们介绍数据的保持和恢复  相信我
However this section, is on persisting and recovering data. Trust me,
我会重新开始码代码的  但是这些理论是与代码紧密相连的
I just want to get us coding again. However, these things are closely linked and
如果你不能完全了解它们的话  就很容易出错  Reito提到
they're easy to get wrong if you don't understand both. As Reito mentioned,
Android把数据保存在Bundle变量中
Android saves the state of the application in bundles. You might have had
你可能认为你已经把所有的信息存在其中
the idea that you would just save all sorts of information in these bundles and
不必担心数据的保持了  但是  问题是
not have to worry about any other form of persistence. But, the thing is,
这些Bundle数据会随着用户在你的主Activity中点击返回键时消失
these bundles go away as soon as the user hits the Back key in
当用户想结束你的应用时
your main activity. It's really important that they do this.
他们就会这么做
When the user chooses to close your activity with the Back key, the expectation
并希望下次打开你的应用时  显示的是默认状态  而不是上次保存的状态
is that next time your activity is displayed, it will be in the default state.
如果用户用Home键或者程序切换键使你的程序转到后台
If the user backgrounds your app using the Home key or the App Switcher,
下次你的Activity被创建时  需要恢复到上次保存的状态  而不是默认状态
the next time your activity is created, it should resume from the current state.